Records of the Council on Hemispheric Affairs, 1975-2002 M1354
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Materials related to Nicaragua, Argentina, Chile, and Haiti; subject files ("Foreign Aid," etc.); miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 431)
- Materials related to Peru, Ecuador, and Argentina; miscellaneous subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 432)
- Materials related to Colombia, Costa Rica, and Argentina; subject files; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 433)
- Materials related to Haiti and Jamaica; subject files ("Annual Human Rights Report," "Latino Community," etc.); miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 434)
- Materials related to Argentina, Bolivia, Paraguay, Haiti, Uruguay, and Cuba; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 435)
- Subject files - "World Bank," "Women's Rights," etc. (clippings, leaflets, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); miscellaneous publications. (Box 436)
- Miscellaneous materials, including "Despachos," 1986-1987 issues. (Box 437)
- Materials related to Nicaragua, Peru, Costa Rica, and Canada; subject files ("Free Press," "Inter-American Development Bank," etc.); miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 438)
- Subject files - "Summit of the Americas, 1998," "The War on Drugs," etc. (clippings, leaflets, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 439)
- Materials related to Brazil; subject files ("News Spots," etc.); miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 440)
- Materials related to Nicaragua, Mexico, and Guatemala; subject files ("U.S. Immigration Matters," etc.); miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 441)
- Materials related to Nicaragua, Suriname, Canada, Colombia, and Guatemala (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 442)
- Materials related to Nicaragua and Colombia; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 443)